

Conor Cresswell

conorcresswell94@gmail.com 0780827419 conorcresswell.github.io

45 Crowther Close, Southampton, England S019 1BX

Professional Skills

Practical Experience with the
Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop,
Illustrator, InDesign, Adobe XD)
Basic Knowledge of After Effects
and Premiere Pro
Practical use of Boostrap CSS
Framework
Email Design using HTML/CSS
Understanding of Brand Identity
and User Experience

Education

The University of Winchester (2013 – 2017)

Studied up to MA (Hons) in Digital Media Practice and graduated with Merit.

Chalfonts Community College (2006 – 2013)

3 A-Levels: Photography (C), Applied ICT (C) and Design & Technology: Product Design 3D (E) 10 GCSEs grades A-C including 1 Diploma grade B in Level 2 Creative and Media

Hi, I'm Conor!

A **Digital Designer** and **Illustrator** based in **Southampton**, **England**

Professional Summary

A self-motivated and productive designer currently working as a Digital Designer for Totaljobs Group. With over three years' experience as a design practitioner creating an array of high-quality digital products using the Adobe Creative Cloud and HTML/CSS/JavaScript.

Experience

Digital Designer for Totaljobs Group - August 2017 to Present

Responsibilities:

Resizing and retouching external clients' marketing material using Adobe Photoshop.

Responsive email design and production using HTML, CSS, and JavaScipt. Designed informative, interactive, and multi-page training guides for office processes on the Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign). Liasing with internal and external stakeholders on multi-channel documents and campaigns.

Managment of internal team projects and managing Junior Digital Designers within the team

Freelance Graphic Designer/Illustrator for Sprechen Digital Marketing - March 2015 to April 2017

Responsibilities:

Rebuilding existing clients' logos as vector images using Adobe Illustrator. Ensuring that all new designs adhere to company values and guidelines. Improving clients' brands by designing logos, banners, and vector illustrations ready for web use.

Communicating directly with stakeholders to build briefs and plans of action.

References available upon request